It's as simple as growth versus profit.
And a lot of trade-offs we deal with
come back to growth versus profit. It's
really hard to do both at the same time.
You know, you could either grow, grow,
grow by making it really easy to
subscribe, or you could juice your
profit by making sure you're not paying
a 30% tax. Which one is important to
you? The answer is going to be different
based on the ambitions of the business
and the current profit profile of the
business. If we needed to scrape
together some extra points of EBITDA
because we're trying to sell or because
we're private equity owned, neither of
which are true, then we'd be thinking
about it very differently. But we're
just trying to grow and provide value to
the maximum number of people, which
leads to a different decision. Hello,
I'm your host, David Bernard. My guests
today are Michael Seagull, CEO, and Mark
Angerer, CPO at Skylight, the family
tech company behind the Skylight frame
and calendar. On the podcast, I talked
with Michael and Mark about the boom in
hardware enabled subscriptions. How
getting the product right unlocked
everything else and doubling their price
to $79
even though the data said they could
charge more. Hey, Michael, thanks so
much for joining me on the podcast
today. Thanks so much for having me,
David. It's really exciting to be here.
>> And Mark, nice to have you as well.
>> It's great to be here. Thanks, David.
>> Really excited to have you guys on the
podcast. Sometime in January, I was
poking around app figures and I started
seeing that hardware enabled
subscriptions kind of had a moment in
the in the 2025 holiday season from uh
Aura Ring and Backbone and Bird Buddy
and and Skylight and I just kept going,
you know, and and searching for more and
more of these hardware enabled
subscriptions and saw downloads
skyrocketing and for those that use
inapp purchase, you know, revenue
skyrocketing. And so it seems like this
category has really taken off over the
last few years. So I'm really excited to
kind of talk through those things with
the two of you. So first thing I did
want to start with was as a hardware
product, what what was the decision and
when was the decision made to layer on a
subscription component? I'm a former VC.
I used to work at Bessemer and Skylight
started out as a digital picture frame
company. Today it's that, but digital
calendars are much more of the business.
And as soon as I went full-time and the
business was couple million in revenue,
there were two of us here. The first
thing we looked at each other is Jake
and I co-founders that were like, "It's
time for a subscription." Just coming
from VC land, a hardware business in
consumer without a subscription is
basically not building enterprise value
uh with rare exception. And so we just
knew two things. number one that we have
to from a business model perspective,
but also the net promoter score of our
product was so high, so off the charts
good that we figured there's something
we can build for you. Basically, the
next things on the future list, we're
just going to put those behind a payw
wall cuz you guys seem to really like
our product. We've built enough goodwill
that we think you'll be willing to pay.
And by the way, you use our product
daily if not or weekly if not daily. So
all the signs pointed to our ability to
do it and that the customers would be
receptive and we kind of knew we had to
from an enterprise value perspective.
>> What was the the timing of this? So when
was the company started and when did you
introduce a subscription? Because I do
feel like when hardware products started
introducing subscriptions, it does feel
like there was some push back and it
took a while for consumers to feel
comfortable having paid often hundreds
of dollars for a hardware product. then
wait I got to pay more and I got to pay
more every single month. So what what
was the timing of this?
>> So first I'll say they're still
uncomfortable and reasonably so. Uh so
we're not just engaging with that
discomfort every day, but we're trying
to figure out the right balance where
people think it's fair and they're not
barfing all over it after paying $300 to
$600. And it's a delicate balance and it
changes every year. the market shifts in
terms of what for your specific product
people are willing to pay for. In our
case, the business was launched in 2015.
We launched the subscription in 2018, so
it was pretty early days. Kind of
getting back to the to this holiday
season, you know, I'm sure you follow
this side of the industry way more than
I do. Are there specific things you
think made this holiday season so great?
I mean, is it just, you know, continuing
acceptance of these kind of products or
what what happened?
>> Yeah, I don't think this season was
unique. I think it's just a crescendo of
something that's been happening for a
few years. If you go in my time hop, I
have screenshots from every December
25th of the past few years. That shows
you in the top 15 apps downloaded on the
app store Christmas Day. It's first of
all, it's been us and then a couple of
our competitors in both the f mostly the
frame category which is the more mature
category and then you know you'll see
Tony Box which is the kids audio
platform. They were number one or number
two this year but they've been up there
for years. So it just seems like more
that these categories are reaching mass
adoption and maturity. And so obviously
during the holidays when you're looking
for something cool to give, you give a
physical product, people love us and a
couple of these other categories. So
just naturally skyrockets to the top of
the charts.
>> Has it been just linear growth or has it
been kind of an exponential like every
year it just gets bigger and bigger cuz
it it does feel like there's just more
hardware enabled subscriptions than
ever. So yeah, just curious if if if
you've seen a pattern.
>> I tend to think of it as market by
market. Like if I'm speaking to a random
entrepreneur and they're like I'm going
to launch a hardware with a
subscription, I'll say don't don't do
that because you know look I mean each
market is its own thing and the frame
market which is now the the Wi-Fi
enabled digital frame market is 10 plus
years old. It's gotten extremely
competitive and kind of commoditized and
blah blah blah blah but yes it's reached
mass mass adoption in the smart calendar
category which we invented. it's much
less commoditized and we're far and away
the leader and it's all really exciting.
So I don't think of it as a mega trend.
It's like you have to have a really good
idea and there's very few and far
between good ideas of a physical thing
that anybody is willing to pay or like
millions of people are willing to pay.
If I had a list of 10 more, we would be
launching those things. But there isn't.
I mean there there's not a hundred
things. And like even some of the
secondary categories like smart pet
cameras and other things, you just don't
see them in the top 50 or 100 cuz
there's very precious few categories
that are going to be new electronics
that reach mass adoption. Maybe I'm just
a total outlier as a wealthy
dude with four kids and and super into
tech, but I just in the last couple of
years got a FI dog collar to track uh my
dog. I got my wife a bird buddy camera
to like and she freaking loves it. And
we were both I mean to be honest and
again even just you know being in the
industry when we were going through the
onboarding and I think it's like $60 or
$90 a year and it was like
wait a minute but she freaking loves it
and I do too and like we have a little
like family group chat with me and the
kids and and my wife and she's like
posting pictures of the bird and the
kids are naming them and like it's just
been this whole thing in our house and
funny enough and part of the reason I
knew about Skylight was that my wife I
don't probably saw Instagram or or
somewhere skylight and asked me like,
"Hey, should we get this?" And I
actually said, "Yeah, go for it." And
she didn't pull the trigger yet yet, but
we'll probably have a skylight in our
house in the not too distant future. So,
maybe I'm a little bit of an outlier,
but it does just feel like I've been uh
accumulating these software enabled and
subscription enabled hardware.
>> I think both things can be true. Like,
you can count on probably two hands the
brands that have broken out. FI, Bird
Buddy, these are great companies. We're
friendly with most of them, but there's
not like 500 of them. Whereas, if you go
into consumer subscription apps, I think
there's much more of a long tale of
really interesting niche plays. Here,
it's just like an order of magnitude
less. But also, the number is going up.
It's just maybe 5 years ago there were
like three of these and now there's like
20 of these, but it's not 200. So, it's
still a pretty high bar in terms of
conquering everything in terms of supply
chain, but also just finding these mass
adoption categories. So, I'm sure
there'll be like Next Playground is the
new hot one that's all a buzz. It's the
kids like movementbased video game
system that's couple hundred bucks plus
a subscription. Uh, and it's it's just
exploded in the past year. So, I think
every year there will be one or two new
ones, but I don't think there will be
like 30 new ones next year. One other
that I forgot to mention is Backbone.
Another fantastic product. I don't know
if you guys have ever used this. You,
you know, connect your iPhone and it
becomes a like a handheld uh turns your
iPhone into a Switch basically like a
handheld gaming machine with controllers
and everything. And I've played
Minecraft with my kids for years and
freaking love having a hardware
attached. that that's the one though
where I don't know what they're I don't
even know what they're offering in their
subscription and have like not been I
guess I don't even like launch the app
because it just kind of works and I just
play Minecraft with my kids on it. But
anyways, yeah, there's just so many um
and Mark I think you had something you
wanted to chime in on.
>> Well, I was going to say you mentioned
that you were looking at app downloads
as a proxy and I would just say that
that's generally a proxy for a device
sold. So it's a really good way to proxy
the growth of the hardware, but the
subscription and the health of the
subscription business. I think our
experiences can vary a ton based on how
critical that device is. So yeah, and
probably a good example would be that
the backbone where um you know every
other one I mentioned almost required a
subscription and with backbone it's just
it's a great device and you know maybe
they're not as successful on the
subscription side of things. And that's
actually something I wanted to get to.
And so we'll just go right there. It's
like, how do you make sure that your
Skylight device is functional for the
$300 they purchase, but then still
entice them with a subscription? How do
you think about the breakdown of what
should be free and kind of maintaining
that good user experience of the free
product and then what you're going to
put behind the subscription? Yeah. So,
uh definitely one that both Mark and I
should comment on because he's going to
have a different angle on this. I think
step one first and foremost is our
devices are daily usage in the home,
right? So, they're always on helping you
either by displaying photos of your
loved ones or by being this full
calendar family management system that
literally is the heartbeat of your home.
So once you've got daily valuable usage
and attention, it's relatively easier to
say, "Hey, we can do more valuable
things for you. Here they are and
they're behind a subscription payw wall
than if you have a device that you put
away and maybe you don't use for a
week." It's And by the way, even
Skylight Frame is harder than Skylight
Calendar cuz it typically sits in mom or
grandma's house sight unseen. And so
you're not thinking about what other
valuable things you could do with it.
And there's also less depth of what you
can do with it versus a thing that runs
your whole family. So calendar is sort
of the perfect storm in terms of a
really deeply valuable thing that you
can have a subscription to. I'd love to
throw it to Mark both to add to that as
well as how we think about where to draw
the line. If you kind of boil it down,
you want the what the customer is
buying, like the heart of like why do
they want this thing to be part of what
they're getting and they're paying for
that $300 or they'll feel sort of
tricked and and duped, right? And so for
frame, I think it was like when you get
down to it, it's like I want to easily
get photos to grandma and you should be
able to do that without a subscription.
and then videos comes up and you're
like, "Oh, it'd be nice to have a video
on there." And that goes in the
subscription and that feels sort of like
it's a natural upsell, but it's not the
core of what you came there for. And the
same thing for us is true in in
calendar. People are coming there and
they're saying, "Well, I want to be able
to organize my events and get my tasks
and to-dos and chores done and those are
things that we include." And then you
go, "Well, what about recipes and meals
and what if we have an AI engine that
helps you get all this done faster?" And
you go, "Well, great. That's a
subscription." And so I think as long as
it passes that gut test of like the
person came there and they spent those
dollars and they got it, we're good.
Where things are getting tricky is
naturally our marketing teams are like,
but that AI feature is super exciting
and people love it. Can we advertise
that? And so you go, okay, well, how do
we start to advertise all the good stuff
about the product or the completeness of
the product without confusing them so
that they buy it and then they feel sort
of like that love and that excitement
turns into surprise or frustration. And
I'd love to just underscore something
Mark said. The heart of I think Mark's
comment, which is the heart of how we
approach this, is it's emotional. We
look in the whites of customers eyes and
we try to figure out what feels
relatively reasonable. Like nobody wants
to pay a subscription, but there's a
spectrum between I get why you're
charging a subscription and I'm feeling
ripped off, angry, and disgust, right?
like when it's something that they feel
on almost a values basis should be free.
The emotion that is elicited is disgust
and anger. And when you're trying to
build a multi-billion dollar brand, that
is not an emotion. Even if it's actually
short-term
subscription maximizing, not an emotion
you want to elicit. So, we have had
times where we put something behind the
payw wall and it makes the numbers go
up, but we learned through reviews and
just interviews that it's very
begrudging or even anger elilliciting.
And our point of view is we want to
steer clear that we're not a get-richqu
scheme here. We're trying to build
something for a generational company. So
we keep our pulse on the emotional
reaction to where the line is, not just
some quant AB test of what performs.
>> That's exactly what I was going to ask
next is do you test things in and out of
the subscription bundle? So it sounds
like yes, you do. So then is there is
there any kind of line you draw like you
kind of lean toward putting something
behind the subscription first and then
you'll pull it out if you hit those
roadblocks or or is it just such a case
by case and do you have any other
examples of something maybe that wasn't
behind the payw wall that you put behind
the payw wall?
>> Well, I can jump in. I think the the
kind of philosophy as you build things
out like we really want anything that
goes into the bundle to like make sense
quickly to a user like they need to gro
it without thinking too hard and we
don't want it to be something that they
stumble into and it's like this
configuration setting they're like a
crap if I want this view I've got to pay
for it like they wouldn't get that when
they're actually buying the product or
signing up for it. So, as we build out
new things that are like, hey, like a
good example was we launched a meal
planning module. And it was like for
people who are meal planners, it's
really clear what that's going to do. I
think I'm going to be able to plan the
family's meals and we said that wasn't
part of the product before. So, you're
still getting the same thing that you
got for $300 for that same $300 and this
new thing that they can gro is going to
go behind the payw wall. And a lot of
those things we don't even test. Like
sometimes we just say, "Hey, that makes
sense." It's obviously easier to start
behind the payw wall when you're adding
something new that passes that. Yeah, I
gro it. I want to test and then move it
out then the other way around is very
painful. So that's kind of how we've
felt our way into it. Also
counterintuitive point number one here
is we have tried changing the
merchandising of how do we show what is
in the bundle to users and those changes
often don't change the attach rate what
we call the attach rate what percent are
subscribing very much. So, a lot of
times we get the sense that as long as
there's value in the bundle and the
customer is excited about Skylight,
they're kind of like, give me the whole
thing. I want this subscription and
they're going to start with it and turn
it on. And this optimizing of how
exactly do we frame it? We haven't yet
seen a ton of change in the attach rates
based on how we rebundle things. I'll
just add a couple of thoughts. One is
sort of I want to put a healthy layer of
humility down. We have never had a
subscription growth product manager. We
are hiring our first one right now and
haven't found them yet. So all of this
when we say we've done this, we've we've
lightly done it. We we've done our best,
but I actually I think I learned this
when I went to your conference like
whoa. Okay, there are some people that
are 10x more rigorous at testing the pay
walls at every step than we are. Cool.
Let's let's do that. But we, as I said,
we have yet to have or find that that uh
perfect growth PM who's going to drive
that for us. So these are all early
instincts, but I do think they've proven
out time and again this sort of emotion
first cautious philosophy. I'll give you
one very ripped from the headlines
example. When we launched in 2018, or
maybe it was early 19 for calendar,
we're like, you know what, we know how
to do photos on a device. We're just
going to put that behind the payw wall.
Like no rigor at all. Uh just like if
you're buying it for a calendar, cool.
if you also want it to be a photo frame,
39 bucks a year, which by the way is a
magic number where people don't really
care that much. And it worked. It just
worked out of the box. But it's now been
8 years and the market has evolved. And
now our customers are telling us that
not overwhelmingly, but some customers
are starting to say much more than 2
years ago, hey guys, this photo screen
saver really should be free. And so
we're having active discussion about do
we make it totally free? Do we make it
partly free? Kind of moving it outside
of the payw wall based on changing
tastes, which it's going to happen over
a decade as the competition and the
market evolves.
>> On that example with the screen saver,
there's also this sort of second order
effect, right? Of the first one is like,
hey, we got more subscribers and AR goes
up. Great. But the second order effect
is people didn't come to buy calendar
for the frame, but we often listen to
customers and they say, boy, I bought it
for the calendar. It's great that we're
organized, but my kids love the photos,
right? And so people who have it just
light up about the product and the
experience and like again unrigorously
we're like that is surely good and
that's going to lead to more top
offunnel. That's going to lead to them
telling their neighbor and their friend
and we're starting to see that happen
more and more and so we go well maybe
that's another reason that you know
we're being shortsighted if we're both
frustrating customers and so we're as
Michael said we're trying to figure out
how can we move beyond fully paywalling
that feature. Yeah, I think you know
most subscription apps who are paying
attention anyway struggle with this is
figuring out what to be behind the payw
wall, not what not to be behind the payw
wall. You know, how do you execute on a
premium strategy? And essentially what
you're doing, it's like you have a $300
one-time purchase to get into it, but
then you're still then running kind of a
premium product just like a premium
subscription that doesn't have hardware.
So, a lot of this thinking I think
applies to any app of not confusing the
users, not frustrating the users,
thinking in the long term. I think it it
it's all super applicable. And then what
you were saying about the attach rate,
too. I just did an interview with uh an
employee at Tinder. uh it'll come out
after this podcast and he was talking
about how they've seen over and over
again there's just a certain person who
will just just wants the best and will
just buy you know for for them it's
whatever the platinum subscription and
and you know they don't even necessarily
use the features they don't necessarily
care it's like I'm in on Tinder and I
just want the best of Tinder and so I
imagine that's maybe comes into play in
that attach rate is that there's a lot
of people who's just This thing is
awesome. I want the best of it.
>> It sure does. However, and by the way,
it does even more so than for an app cuz
they are going through the very obvious
gate of buying a really expensive piece
of hardware. So, they're quite motivated
to have the best already. But again, on
a 10 to 15 year business lifespan, you
kind of get through the I guess I'll use
a geological analogy. You get through
the sand and the bedrock, the easy
drilling of people who just really want
your thing. And then you start to hit,
you know, dense, deep stone, which is
people who are like, they really should
have your thing, but they're more
skeptical. They're more price conscious.
They're just thinking about it a lot
more. It's the classic uh crossing the
chasm journey of technology adoption.
And those people are going to process
everything from your product to your
subscription completely differently. So,
you have to continue to appeal to the
first group, but start to widen
uh your positioning, including your
pricing and subscription for the next
group. It's hard.
>> And speaking of which, in the uh in the
prep for the podcast, you shared people
don't assess what they are paying for as
logically as you think. You're you're
kind of alluding to that, but I wanted
you to maybe dig a little deeper what
you meant by that.
>> Yeah, I'm happy to take that one. So I
think you know when we we speak with a
number of growth PMs and folks that come
from the premium world where it's like
download the app and this they have this
giant user base from which to pick and
in that in that relationship with the
customer it's like well they got
something for free the user shows up and
then they try to basically sell them on
the value give them a taste of all the
features but because of the dynamics
we've been talking about here which is
like mom has been thinking for six
months about this purchase they've been
on our website and Reddit and they're
doing the YouTube reviews they've made
that decision to go allin. And so that
instinct to say like, well, you've got
to convince them that it's worth $3.99 a
month and they're doing some calculation
in their brain of what's the alternative
to that is like, yes, there are some
customers who do that for sure. Got a
diverse customer base. The point there
is like most are actually not doing that
once they've made that decision to buy.
They just want to know that this is
really valuable. They're going to be
using it every day. It's meaningful for
their family. And then I'll add a little
trick. We don't actually in our product
call out what is a premium plus feature
if you are subscribed which I think
makes a pretty big difference as the
person is thinking about when it's
renewal time and they're going okay well
I'm paid $79 a year right now for that
like what did our family get from these
and what was in the bundle and did I use
this like that if that's your intuition
as a product person is like that's not I
think what's normally happening and we
see renewal rates are pretty high even
across folks that heavily use the bundle
and those that don't but That's because
all what's common across all of those
customers, the device is on, they're
regularly using it, and it's bringing a
lot of value to their families overall.
They want the full thing. Um, and so
that's what we mean by not being too
overly fixated, at least in a hardware
business. I can imagine a non-h hardware
business, the relationship might be
different and more tenuous to those free
users than what it is to our free users
who actually paid $300 and have a
physical thing on their kitchen counter
they see every day. One thing I was
curious about and I I should have just
done more research, but I think it might
be an interesting topic if if you have
thought about it. Is there a software
only experience? Like as you're building
out all of these tools, and we'll get to
the whole family OS concept later, but
is there a software only experience
where people can use some of these
scheduling tools and other stuff,
whether it's, you know, on a home, like
we have an iMac that sits in the old
like 10-year-old iMac that sits in the
living room. Um and like could could we
just run that on our iMac or or is it
for now just a hardware only experience?
>> So your intuition about software only is
astute. Although I think that particular
implementation may not be the right one.
High level again if you want to be a
generational company if you want to be
the operating system for families not
everyone is going to buy a piece of
hardware. Not everyone is visual. Not
everyone thinks they need it. So can we
but but the problem is the physical
presence is a lot of the value right
it's like that's what gets everybody in
the family in sync and having
conversation so you get rid of that and
you just have another family calendar uh
well we are not convinced that that is a
super valuable juicy wonderful
experience to put into the world at
least not until AI showed up and that's
where we're getting really interested to
what extent can a smart AI family
assistant substitute for that physical
presence with its relationship that it
builds and the way that it communicates
with all your family members all at once
and gets everybody aligned and on track.
Interesting question, right? So that's
where we're trying to figure out a
softwareonly solution. The people who
tend to bring it up are often very tech
forward, very male and so we've never
really decided to pursue it. It didn't
feel mass market. Yeah, David, my
favorite one-star reviews that we
receive take the form of, "This is dumb.
It should be an iPad app, but my wife
loves it." I go, "Okay, I guess that's a
one-star review." Um, so the point is
like the form factor really really
matters. And this bring your own device
is like, you know, I'm I'm not sure
that's a huge unlock for us beyond
trying to figure out how to how do we
solve through an app and an assistant
that really helps the family. But
>> yeah, it's funny. the deeper we get into
this conversation, the more sold I am on
the on the product be partly just the
vision you have and and I I think my
wife and my family would would really
love it. I did want to dig in and you
know I don't know exactly how much you
want to share but you know I'm always
curious about this sort of thing with a
hardware attached subscription. How much
of the business is hardware or is a
hardware a break even or a loss leader
or you know I would imagine different
companies approach this differently but
I'm curious how you think about that. So
the right way to run the business by the
textbook would be to run the hardware at
contribution zero and just build this
juicy giant ARR business. That said,
Skylight is bootstrapped and profitable.
And that logic leads you to spend, you
know, the the customer acquisition curve
is sort of has this sort of fall off a
cliff effect where you could tell your
marketers spend $130 to acquire
customers and then you say, no, we're
going to spend to to contribution zero.
spend 180 200 and you get like zero more
customers. You just light $50 million on
fire. So we've tended to make money off
of both. We make a bit of money off the
hardware, make a good amount of money
off the software such that the profit
I'm the question I'm going to answer
first is about half and half. Now that's
going to change this year because you
may know that the entire computing
industry is in a massive crisis in terms
of memory supply. So memory prices are
out of control. everyone's laptops are
going to be really expensive. Skylight,
because we have the luxury, is going to
keep our prices the same and just not
make money on the hardware essentially
uh and make all of our money on the on
the software. And then maybe in a future
year it'll be both again. But I will
just add the caveat when you have a
hardware business, you're in this unique
position where the revenue is like this
big, right? And so people are always
like, "What percentage is subscription
of your total revenue?" Well, the thing
is we sell millions and millions of
units and we're growing really fast. So,
the subscription never has a chance to
catch up, right? You you pay $300 to
$700 for a device and then you pay 80
bucks a year. Some fraction of people
pay that. So, you can do the math. It's
never going to be 50% of the business
until the day when the calendar hardware
business plateaus and then over time
software will catch up. So it's a good
problem to have that you know software
might be I don't know 10 to 20% of our
revenue but it is half of the profit. So
you're you're right about that. Keeping
the price to a level where we can
generate the demand profitably feels
like a little bit of dry powder for us
in the positive sense right both for who
would have seen the memory shock coming
maybe we should have seen around that
corner a year ago but we're in a good
spot because of that. Same with tariffs.
Last year when there was a moment where
Vietnam was going to get crushed, we
were not sweating bullets. And then
there's also like if we want to generate
demand, we can go down. And we've talked
earlier in this about how it's hard to
go the other way. Um and so it feels
like the strategy served us really well
as we've been growing into a new market
that that we've created. Yeah. And
certainly if we'd raised funding, I can
imagine the $und00 million check hits
the bank and it's like drop the prices
and like get to three times as many
households. And like that is a strategy
for sure. Um, and it's not that not the
path we've taken.
>> Can I just riff on that for one second?
My one of my favorite topics is how do
you bootstrap a business like this? And
it's super simple but really hard to do,
which is there's three reasons you're
not going to bootstrap. One is to build
the software. Like you need you need
engineers. That's becoming less of a
thing in an AI world. You need working
capital to buy all of your units before
Christmas. That's really hard, maybe for
a different podcast, but I'm happy to go
into it. And then there's the marketing
cost. And this is what every
subscription marketer probably knows,
and if not, you should know. Just pay
back on the first order. Do whatever you
humanly can to pay back on day zero
because then you have no marketing
payback time. With Skylight, with a
hardware business, you have the added
benefit that we're selling a thing,
right? So like a physical thing. So, we
pay back, every single order in the
company's history has paid back on day
zero. There's no marketing acquisition
cost, which means you don't have to go
convince a bunch of VCs to give you $20
million just to to grow, which is
awesome. So, if you're doing a new
subscription and it's like five bucks a
month, just figure out how to make it
that 60 to $70 a year upfront payment
and you're golden on your CPA and your
payback time. The the one thing I did
see in researching and anybody who
listened to this episode and you know
wants to enter this or or is just more
curious will see that you did do some I
believe some form of venture debt or
like inventory debt. I you know this
won't be super applicable to our most of
our audience but I am curious just a
brief overview of in a hardware business
that kind of facility is really
important and but it's not actually
raising money. So, how did that work?
Give me the, you know, two-minute
overview.
>> In the early days, I had I personally a
weekly cash flow model because you could
be at zero cash in the bank and then
millions the next day if the next day is
Black Friday. By the way, you have to
buy all your inventory weeks in advance
for it to be produced, shipped over. So,
you have to play this incredibly
delicate cash planning game in a way
that most businesses. And by the way,
even most hardware businesses or
physical goods, like if you're in
cosmetics, you don't care cuz your your
cost of goods is 10%. Our cost of goods
is like 50%. So, we're spending insane
amounts of money to just buy the stuff.
Now, your point is you don't have to
raise venture. Well, yes and no. It
depends how fast you're growing. If
we're like, we want to grow 4x and we
need this much money. Well, the problem
is the bank is going to say, "I'm not on
board with that. That's scary. What if
you don't grow at all or you, you know,
shrink? Then we've lost all of our money
and we're sitting on a bunch of
inventory that, by the way, we can't
even sell because it's connected device.
You need to be around to run it." So,
we've been incredibly prudent about
growing fast, but not too fast, and then
finding lenders who are more risk
friendly than a bank, but less expensive
than debt. It's that happy middle of
there were times when we paid 15 to 20%
annualized, but it made sense when you
do our profit numbers to do that instead
of raising equity. We could afford it. I
I would trade off gross margins all day
long instead of selling a piece of the
company. So, that's what we did. We
found those creative lenders and we
still work with fantastic
uh I don't I don't know if people say
fantastic and we love them about their
lenders, but they're fantastic and we
love them and we're very lucky to have
found them and I think they're happy
with us. So, it's that finding that
really good relationship with somebody
who gets what you're doing and is
willing to charge more for for a little
bit more risky debt basically. And we do
see this starting to to happen in the
software only side of things as well.
Like ladder raised a hund00 million
facility with General Catalyst for user
acquisition and very similar things.
It's like they could have gone out and
raised more venture capital, but why
take the dilution when General Catalyst
has a fantastic product to get access to
tens or hundreds of millions of dollars
if you're the right product and the
number the the math works. So yeah, it's
kind of fascinating how that there are
similarities and how people look at, you
know, raising venture versus finding
another facility to fund that cash flow,
whether it is to buy hardware or to fund
user acquisition. The next thing I
wanted to ask about is how you see this
hardware device as a software moat. you
know, you you've kind of alluded to it
already is that once somebody puts this
up in their home, probably not coming
off the wall unless they just stop using
it or move and forget to put it up or
whatever, but hopefully you're creating
enough value. So, how do you think about
that balance of like the hardware is a
moat, but you still really got to do
your job to keep them retained both on
the subscription but then also retained
as a user.
>> So, I mean, first of all, it's totally
true, right? Once they've invested in
the hardware and they have it in their
household, that's protective of that
customer. But that I mean, if we step
all the way back, we've got a we're in
maybe 2 million households today.
There's 100 million households in the
US, 30 million with kids are, you know,
so we're in the 10 to 20 million maybe
market size. So like we're in the early
stages here. So we don't sleep super
well feeling like, well, just because
some we're in some households today that
that's not a future mode and the market
is still yet to be won, right? We're
hope we're a tenth of the way there. So
yes, it's true for the existing
customer, which is great for our
retention. You know, we have very high
retention rates and that cuts across the
different types of features, as I
mentioned, that they use. There's
actually not a super high correlation
there because people are are in it. So,
it is protective for that customer you
acquire, but uh but not for future
customers.
>> It's interesting though, like I know
hardware is all the rage right now, but
hardware is the most cutthroat
competitive world. Sometimes compared to
software, I feel like it's a 100x
crazier. Like we had competitors who
fully cloned and ripped off our UI UX
and just sold it to hundreds of Chinese
OEMs who now populate Amazon with what
we consider pretty mediocre products,
but people looking for a cheap deal are
buying them at at times. That's wild. So
So to your point about moes, let's be
real. Like hardware is not actually a
moat. It's a mode against people who
don't know how to do hardware, but it's
not a long-term 20-year mode in a
market. In fact, I would say neither
hardware nor software
are modes anymore. It's got to be
something that your competitors cannot
do or are not willing to do. And no
amount of software is that, especially
in a world where software development is
getting progressively easier. So, it's
got to be either classic moes like
network effects or ecosystem modes like
partnerships or a developer platform uh
around your thing. Something where
people look at two identical pieces of
hardware and software and still pick us.
What would make them still pick us that
other people can't have? Well, let's
start with, you know, retailers. We're
in Costco and Best Buy and and a bunch
of others and that's, you know, they're
only going to take one player generally.
So, that's a good moat. other
partnerships that we're exploring that
are really exciting also a potential
moat. But it's it's darn hard to switch.
You're essentially asking us or we're
asking ourselves to switch from a
software/h hardware utility which
ultimately someone can clone to a
utility plus ecosystem consumer or
business partner or whatever some
ecosystem that others cannot clone. That
that's not trivial. Everyone always when
I'm chatting with them like you should
think of some network effects. Cool.
Well, thank you. Yeah, we're we're
thinking. But you can't just tack it on.
It has to be incredibly authentic to
what the product does. But if you have
that, if you have that, you've got the
best business in the world.
>> I'm reminded of the like my profit is
somebody else's opportunity here, right?
And so somebody in the audience is
thinking, wait, so you've kept your
prices high and you've got a juicy
subscription. Like somebody's paying
attention and like, yeah, that's, you
know, go on Amazon and you'll you'll see
that. And so that's why we're trying to
basically move faster. So I think the
short-term moat is certainly not
long-term but the short-term moat is
have the best product move quickly and
always be ahead. So whenever our
customer is doing research they come
back to if I want the best product the
category defining product the Kleenex of
this product like it has to be us and if
we maintain that position then good
things happen like Costco and others
will want to work with us because we are
the product that the customer demands
most even at a premium. Um and so you
know we kind of think of like the if we
can have the Apple model here where yeah
maybe in the long run we're not the vast
majority of all devices sold but we are
the vast majority of the profit that's
the position that we would want to to
take.
>> So how do you think about getting that
message across? I wanted to talk about
growth next and I think that was like
the perfect segue is from influencers to
paid marketing to how you show up in
retail. How do you position yourself as
that best product and what are the
levers you're currently pulling on
growth?
>> Yeah. So, I I'm going to cheat and say
that the before any of that, you
actually have to be the best product. We
learned this the hard way. Uh back when
we were developing like calendar was
born, it was a glint in my eye and and
Jake, my CTO's eye, in July 2018, we're
like easy, let's launch it. We launched
it in November. I think that's when we
shipped November 2018. our first units.
It took until fall 22 to take off. And
the macro mistake that we made is we
starved it from a it turned out it was
really hard to build. It was not digital
picture frames. Was really hard to
figure out what people wanted and build
a deep software experience that could
run people's lives. And we tried we
gunned marketing in 21 and 22 revved the
engine and it just kind of sucked. It
didn't work. And we thought about
killing the product. We're like this
this is depressing. and this business
isn't working and we're ignoring the
other business that is working. But the
root of it was our product sucked. So to
any entrepreneurs out there debating
whether to allocate resources to product
and marketing, if your product isn't
like a solid 40 NPS, I think marketing
effort and dollars are kind of a waste
of time cuz you're going to get a false
negative. People aren't going to want
it. You're not going to know if it's cuz
your marketing sucks or your product
sucks. Now flash forward. Our product
rocks. We're very proud and it's getting
so much better every single month. It's
amazing, but you're still building a new
technology. Technology adoption curves
are rough, especially after you get past
the early adopters. So, sure, paid
growth is great. And in a business like
digital picture frames, that's all you
needed cuz it was like everybody
understood your idea. Come Christmas or
Mother's Day, all it took was two ads
and people just bought it. This
calendar, people have to commit almost
spiritually to change the way they're
running their family. They're like, I
need a better way. That is a multimonth
emotional journey that they're going on.
So, how do we help them on that journey?
A, I have no idea. If you know, tell me
because we're just trying to figure it
out.
>> That growth PM you need to hire.
Somebody in this audience go apply for
that job.
>> Yes, please, please. And thank you. Uh,
but like influencers are huge and very
authentic. You know, people can smell an
inauthentic influencer, but someone we
have a thousands of people out there
using this, loving it, talking about it.
that plus paid growth. Retail is the
biggest influencer of all in our world.
Like the fact that we're in Costco and
other great retailers, it's a stamp of
quality that can't be underestimated.
So, it's kind of that. And the fourth
part of the the square is just word of
mouth, right? We often poll our
customers and we ask, "How impactful is
this thing to you?" Like, is it
life-changing? Pretty high bar. Is it
like very awesome but not life-changing
or is it worse than that? Today about
20% of people who reply say that it's
life-changing. And our hypothesis is
those are the people who are getting us
dozens and dozens of new customers just
by virtue of they can't stop talking
about it. But not life-changing is
probably an order of magnitude in terms
of the chatter and how good our business
is. So probably the best thing we could
do for growth long term is just build
build build features that take us into
50% life-changing territory. So that
that's Mark as our chief product officer
that is pretty much explicitly his goal.
The other thing that we've done is we've
decided to be multi- channelannel right
and so this is something that those who
are not in hardware are not thinking
about but we have our own website where
we sell the product and we directly
control the relationship with the
customer. We sell through Amazon and we
sell through retailers and we do the
same thing internationally. And so I
think the strategy to be everywhere that
has been very successful for us, but it
comes with real complexities and
trade-offs. Um, and we could probably do
a whole podcast just on how to be multi-
channelannel. The point I would make
here for subscription focused audiences
in our owned channel on mys skylight.com
we have a much higher attach rate to the
subscription because we can turn the
subscription on automatically and we
actually like pro tip here we give a
discount on the hardware if you sign up
with the subscription and that is a
super successful way to get subscribers
cuz it seems like a great deal. Wait, I
get a free month and I pay less today
and I'm getting the full access and I
can choose to opt out. Most people
don't. We can't do that on Amazon. We
can't do that in a retailer and so those
channels behave differently for the
subscription.
>> And bringing it back to the other point
that as uh retail becomes heavier and
heavier in our mix that puts enormous
pressure on us to be able to prove to
our customers downstream of purchase
that there's all this, you know, hey,
you're not just here for a calendar.
That part's free. You're here for the
full family operating experience. The
problem is when people are setting this
thing up, there's like laser focused on
getting it up on the wall as a calendar.
It's really freaking hard to tell them,
"Oh, by the way, we do meals and recipes
and to-dos." And you should set all
those things up. And by the way, chores
for your kids is really cool. Take 10
minutes and really think about your your
chore system. And then once they have, I
would say within weeks, if not days,
after they've established their kind of
natural daily flows and cadence in the
app, our ability to convince them to try
new things kind of drops to zero. again,
maybe growth PM can help us, but it's
really freaking hard once they have a
established pattern of behavior. So,
there's this iceberg underneath of an
incredibly useful software and they know
it's probably useful, but they're like,
I'm a busy mom. At some point, I really
should check all that out. And then they
never do. So, this is the nut that Mark
is trying to crack this year cuz that's
also where all the subscription stuff
is, right? We like sort of love and hate
that how common customers tell us like,
"I love my skylight and I know it can do
so much more." And I actually have
friends when I talk to who just bump
into happen to have a Skylight and they
hear I work at Skylight. They almost
feel they need to apologize. It's like,
"Oh no, I I like it, but like I I know
it can do so much more. Like, don't quiz
me on all of it." And then you're kind
of going, "Yeah, there's just a lot of
stuff being left on the table there."
And to Michael's point, the data shows
us after 30 days, it's pretty hard to
change their behaviors. So, our newer
customers that set up the device with
more features tend to use those things
more. The older customers, their habits
are set, the family set, and what that
device means to them. So, yeah, maybe
somebody can help us change that, but
it's been hard. Um, and just one other
fun idea, which I think is relevant to
your audience. In a world of like web
2.0 onboarding where you just have
screens and you fill them out and it's
kind of cumbersome, your ability to
educate people about a bunch of
different features is quite limited. But
what about in a future world of
AIdriven, maybe even conversational
onboarding? You could probably
accomplish a great deal more in terms of
in the same 10 minutes you have with
them. You could get them set up on a
full chore chart if they, hey, my kids
are eight and three. Boom, boom, boom.
Here's here's some sample chores. Do any
of these ring a bell for you? So, this
is the sort of stuff we're thinking
about. How do you squeeze more and more
aha moments early on in their
experience? Cuz squeezing them in after
30 days pretty hard.
>> And something we're thinking about there
is like well today kind of an amazing
fact is Skylight's gotten to where it is
from a subscription perspective without
a free trial. Um and that is like so
table stakes presumably for the other
folks that you you talk with. And the
reason for that is because we have that
own channel and because in our
downstream flows we see most people
decide to subscribe up top back to that
I want the full bundle give me it all
that there is only an an incremental
number that will subscribe after that.
So if we tell everybody there's a free
trial. I think it will actually be
counterproductive. And so I'm sure
there's a way for us to crack this nut
but we haven't done that yet. Which
means this idea of like get them in give
them access to all these things and then
they'll they'll like it. use it and
they'll they'll stick is something
that's been tricky because of that
nature of people signing up upfront. Bit
of a puzzle there.
>> And that was something I was going to
ask about too is that I know a lot of
hardware enabled subscriptions don't
charge via inapp purchase because there
aren't required to. So like I have an
Aura Ring and you know some of these
others I've talked about are apps. Uh
the FI caller is an app that you can't
subscribe within the app. Was that a
conscious choice? Did Apple ask you to
do that or why why do you have it in app
purchase?
>> I believe Michael you can correct me if
I'm wrong because this predates me but I
believe Apple asked us to do that even
though we had the hardware and obviously
things have changed with what Apple's
requires now so we could move outside of
Apple but in the tests that we've run
and we've only done really one good one.
It pays for itself. So, I've been a
little bit dragging my feet, if I'm
honest, over that being this big juicy
pot of, you know, because it's like a
fraction of our customers are
subscribing on Apple because we have the
direct channel and then of that it's 30%
and in year two it's 15% and some
percent will not subscribe. And so, it's
like it seems like this juicy pot of
money that for me at least has in the
tests we've done has kind of paid itself
off in an increased conversion through
reduced friction. And so,
>> yeah, I think that's the money quote.
It's reduced friction, right? In a world
where they were equally easy, then, you
know, of course there's no incentive.
But I don't think they're yet equally
easy. There's still some extra clicks
and some extra kind of UI weirdness if
you're going to take them to your
website. So, it's kind of the same
reason we're in retail, right? It would
be much easier to just be direct to
consumer. Retailers are hard demanding.
But if you want to be and by the way, if
you want to be a hundred million dollar
business or 50 million or even 200, you
might not need to do any of that. But if
the scope of ambition is to is take over
the world level, you kind of have to be
everything everywhere all at once uh
including I suspect you can't get away
from Apple uh subscriptions.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
And it's funny because a lot of folks
who, you know, have to use inapp
purchase are very excited about the web
and, you know, with the Epic ruling and
other things, there's opportunity, but
that there's almost an overfocus on it
at times where like pick up pick up the
lowhanging fruit. Like it's not all just
free cash flow. You're not going to
automatically make 30%. It's more like
20. And then is it easy? Do your
customers like it? I mean, I was just
dealing with we have a subscription to
the New York Times that we cannot figure
out where it's coming from. Like I've
gone through all my New York Times, my
wife has gone through all her accounts
and we're having to email back and forth
with their support to figure out like
what account our credit card is attached
to just so that we can cancel it. And so
there is that aspect of the consumer
friendly and consumers being really
liking inapp purchase. that I think
moving everything to the web isn't the
best solution for your customers because
a lot of them do prefer to pay through
Apple.
>> Yep. And I'll just put a crisp little
framework in front of you. It's as
simple as growth versus profit. And a
lot of trade-offs we deal with come back
to growth versus profit. You It's really
hard to do both at the same time. So in
this case, you know, you could either
grow grow grow by making it really easy
to subscribe or you could juice your
profit by making sure you're m you're
not paying a 30% tax. Which one is
important to you? The answer is going to
be different based on the ambitions of
the business and the current profit
profile of the business, right? Like if
we needed to scrape together some extra
points of EBITDA for whatever reason
because we're trying to sell or because
we're private equity owned, neither of
which are true, then we'd be thinking
about it very differently. But we're
just trying to to grow and provide value
to the maximum number of people, which
leads to a different decision.
>> Yeah. Fascinating. On the subject of the
subscription, I know a while back you
increased your price and you mentioned
it earlier in the in the podcast about
the $39 being this magical price where
people don't think about it, but you
increased your price from that magical
price to $79 a year. What what was a
thought process behind that and how how
did things go?
>> Yeah. Well, I mean the big picture
thought process was how do we increase
average revenue per user? And there's
two ways to do that. you get more
percent of the people who buy the
hardware to subscribe or you increase
the price. And we actually have more
than half of the families that buy a
calendar subscribing already. And so
there was a sense of like can only get
that a little like we could we could do
more things to try to get more people to
subscribe. But price is really the
biggest lever and also we're likely
leaving value on the table because of
how important and critical this device
is versus our historical reference of
frame. And this is a very skylight
specific thing, but we, you know, to
move fast, the initial calendar
subscription and frame subscription was
literally the same subscription, same
skew, same price point, turned it on for
both devices. The customer didn't know
that, but if they bought another one, it
would have worked. And so it was just
sort of like, hey, we're at 39. And then
we started thinking, well, like if we
were going to do this as a new company
and we were just going to make calendar,
what would we price the subscription at?
We actually just run a bunch of tests.
And this is classic. I'm sure folks in
the audience have all done this, but we
ran a bunch of different variants and we
variated both the price of the
subscription as well as the discount on
the hardware. So that's another pro tip
for the hardware folks out there is like
the relationship between those two
changes the conversion in hardware and
the attached to software, right? And so
you're having margin changes on how many
units you sell, what's your margin per
unit, and how many subscriptions you
sell. And so we did a bunch of tests on
that and we landed at 79. It was
actually not the arpoo maximizing
amount. So, I like to share this one
that like our test showed us that 99
would have made us more when you
calculate all the numbers in the
spreadsheet. It was like a little bit
better, right? It wasn't like massively
better. And so, it's kind of like why
don't we do that? And it was like I
don't know, it just felt like
overreaching, right? We were doubling
our price. We want good vibes to
continue. We can always go up. Um, and
so we landed at 79 as sort of a middle
ground where we we felt pretty confident
going to that change that it was going
to work because of that testing. And
it's it's been phenomenally successful.
There's so much qualitative surveying
and conversations happening throughout
all of this. So if there are any folks
listening who are not constantly talking
to customers either in surveys or
ideally also face toface one-on-one
focus groups, you will see it. You'll
see it very quickly when you meet with
people. And we knew 99 on paper pencled
a little bit better, but that was
getting into closer to that disgust or
like it's not worth it yet territory. We
will revisit that as we stuff more and
more valuable stuff in there. I don't
think it's there yet, but my point is
commercial for doing lots and lots of
research and talking to customers
yourselves. You'll just very clearly see
what the market wants. And then of
course you do some quant testing and
variance cuz sometimes people say
things, they do completely different
things. So you have to do both. But
smart people by doing both can I I tend
to think triangulate to the right
answer. The biggest mistake I would say
people make out there is
not doing the call uh and just like
saying the numbers are going to be what
the numbers are.
>> One tactical question. Did you announce
the price raise before you raise the
price and did was that a nice like bump
in in subscription attach?
>> We did not announce it and we did not
apply it to our existing customer base.
they were grandfathered in through what
we now call legacy plus that has access
to the frame and calendar. So it really
just showed up as the new price for new
customers. And we had a policy that said
if you were on the fence cuz remember we
talked about people are thinking about
it for a while. We didn't want anyone to
feel miffed like I thought it was 39.
I've been thinking about it for 5 months
and I just missed the boat. If they
reached out to us, we honored the old
price effectively indefinitely. So if
anybody's listening today and wants just
bought the skylight and is like I want
that January last year price, email us
and we'll we'll honor it. That seemed to
basic I mean that's kind of one of the
benefits of us being in an early growth
stage and a lesson here is like be
really nice to the existing customers
build for the next 10 million customers
and don't try to squeeze every penny
out. We certainly could have figured out
a way to do that and we had the math on
yeah it's worth a couple million dollars
but we just said let's focus on bigger
and better things. And by the way, if if
there's anyone out there imagining or
not sure what life under private equity
ownership would feel and look like,
private equity people are not mean or
bad or all generally I I have friends
and I I love talking to them, but a
decision like that would go very
differently if you're a PE firm that
needs to sell in four or five years and
double IDA in the process. And it can
lead to some strange short-sighted
decision-m. Well, I I asked in part
because I I haven't had anybody on the
podcast yet. I haven't not talked to
anybody yet who's done a price increase
and announced it ahead of time, but it
seems like that could be a nice little
hack if you have a huge premium base,
which you know, I guess maybe you didn't
have quite as many people to kind of
advertise this to, but if you're going
to raise the price, like last year, I uh
I was working on fitting out my home
gym. And there was this one company,
French Sport, that would announce ahead
of time, hey, on this date, we're going
to raise the prices because of tariffs,
but we wanted to let everybody know. And
a lot of other home gym companies, they
they would just overnight raise a price.
And so one day to the next. And
honestly, like there were a few pieces
that I bought specifically because I was
like, man, I'm never going to get this
price again. So, somebody out there is
going to run this test. And I'll get
them on the podcast and and uh we'll
figure out how how well it works or
doesn't work. All right. I did want to
wrap up with the the three questions I
now ask every guest. And one or both of
you can chime in on these, but I want to
start with what's the biggest win of the
last year? an experiment you did, a
change you implemented. What was your
biggest win of the last year?
>> It has to be the plus subscription uh
going from 39 to 79 with minimal uh loss
of retention and or attach I mean the
the ARR curve you can see it it just was
transformative to the business. Mark led
the entirety of that start to finish to
me. I mean there's many many wins but
even it's coincidental that we're on a
subscription podcast. I would have said
it even if we weren't on a subscription
podcast. That was huge, huge uh win.
>> I'll throw in in dollars, much less, but
in percents, a big win was changing our
checkout flow back to the Apple thing.
We used to have on our device, if
somebody was not subscribing and they
scanned a QR code, it would lead to a
web-based checkout. We flipped that to
Apple and we saw over 100% increase in
conversion. Now, the number of people
that were doing that was smaller, right?
So again, it wasn't like the the 2x
factor of the price that affected
everybody, but just reducing that
friction of like mom pulls out her
phone, scans a QR code, bang, she's
subscribed over 100% lift um from a
change in a QR code.
>> Wow. Yeah, that's great. So what was the
biggest fail of the year? The experiment
that went off the rails, the product
change that pissed a lot of people off.
What was what was the biggest fail of
the last year and what did you learn
from it?
>> I'd go with a free trial test. Um, we
tried to do a free trial where we would
take a customer's credit card and we did
one without with not taking the
customer's credit card. So, we did both
variants and that was not successful in
getting us any additional lift. It was
more or less like the people who opted
into the free trial was roughly the same
as the people who just would have
subscribed. And so, I, you know, this
goes back to our need for a real growth
PM to to tell us how this should
actually work. I'm sure there's an
unlock there, but that was unsuccessful.
>> That to me is actually a resourcing
fail. You can't like moonlight growth
PMing when you have 5% of your road map
available to do it because the first
test is going to fail and you need to
run like eight more and we didn't have
the time to run eight more. So we
basically it was a little bit of a Hail
Mary which is not how you want to be uh
running your efforts.
>> Yeah. I I had the uh chief product
officer of Duolingo on the podcast
recently and it was surprising to me
that for them a free trial was super
successful because it I mean like your
product it's a premium product you're
getting to experience so much of the
value already and so once you've made
the decision you purchase but for them
the free trial was super successful. So
yeah maybe there is there is some way to
to revisit that experiment and make it
work. Uh but but you know it's like
every product's different so who knows
but yeah fa fascinating that it didn't
work for you. All right the last
question is growth would be easier if
well my cheap answer here and I think I
had this ahead of time was if we had a
team for it right if we were able to
experiment and test more. Um so as but
absent being able to do a lot of the
experimentation we're forced to pick
very carefully what we're going to do.
So right now like last year it was like
we're going to do one or two things. And
I think in talking to other folks in
growth, there's a sense of like, well,
we can test a lot and we're going to run
a lot of experiments and I don't know
what's going to work. And the last two
years has instilled in me some sense of
like I really want to know what's going
to work cuz I only get a few shots. Um,
and so growth would be would be easier
if we didn't have that sense of let's uh
really pick carefully. I'll give you
another cheap answer, which is growth
would be easier if we dropped the price
of the hardware. there is meaningful
price elasticity, but we can't at least
not yet for for complex reasons, but
over time, I think if we want to get to
20 million households, that is what's
going to have to happen.
>> Wow, great answer. All right. Well, as
we wrap up, you've already shouted out
you uh very desperately want PM, and
this is a perfect audience to make that
pitch to, but any other open roles or
anything else you wanted to uh shout out
as we wrap up?
>> That's the big one. So, thanks for for
letting us uh mention it.
>> Awesome. Well, thank you so much for
joining me. This is a super fun
conversation. I think folks, even though
it's hardware and not a lot of folks
listening, will, you know, uh be working
on hardware, I I think there's so many
lessons for anybody in the subscription
app space to learn from. So, thanks for
sharing.
>> Thank you. We really appreciate you
having us. Thanks for letting us share
the story.
>> Thanks so much for listening. If you
have a minute, please leave a review in
your favorite podcast player. You can
also stop by chat.subclub.com
to join our private community.